ferraristore.com 2016-05-15

# Privacy Policy

The personal data you provide, by means of registration to the FerrariStore website or by  submitting a purchase order, to Ferrari S.p.A. ('Ferrari') and triboo digitale s.r.l.(triboo digitale s.r.l.'), the online distributor for Ferrari's branded products and web manager  of store.ferrari.com, (hereinafter together also referred to as 'the Companies' or the 'Controllers') will be processed with respect of the principles set forth by the Directive 95/45/CE on personal data protection and by the national legislation of the Controllers regarding the protection of personal information and, in any event, with the principles of confidentiality on which the Companies business is based.

  **Navigation data**  
triboo digitale's web servers automatically record certain information concerning the electronic access systems you use, such as the name of your Internet supplier, the Internet page it comes from, the Internet page(s) visited on our site, the date and the length of the visit.   

 **IP Address**  
The identification of the IP addresses is necessary for the management of our Internet site and in particular for the diagnosis and prevention of technical problems, unauthorised intrusion and/or possible excessive use of various services offered by the site. IP addresses are not usually connected to information allowing to  identify you.     

**1\. Purpose of the processing**  
The personal details you  provide to Ferrari and triboo digitale s.r.l. will be used: to manage your registration and access to the 'store.ferrari.com' website; to allow you to take advantage of services, contents and activities especially reserved to registered users; for the management and execution of your purchase orders; to allow you to take advantage of the  assistance services and/or after-sales warranties; to reply to any of your requests and for technical/organisational communications.  
You will also have the option to consent (see paragraph 8 below) to the use of your personal data for the following additional purposes: to organize and hold events including those of a promotional nature;  to carry out statistical and market surveys and research; to send information and/or promotional communication, including commercial information, in particular our newsletter, advertising material and/or offers of goods and services through the Post, Internet, telephone, e-mail, MMS, SMS from Italy or abroad (including from Countries not belonging to the European Community) exclusively by Ferrari, and/or parent companies and/or allied companies or by any person or legal entity collaborating in the marketing and business activities of Ferrari, Triboo included.

  **2\. Processing means and methods**  
Your personal data will be processed using suitable paper, electronic and/or telematic means  according to fair business practices  strictly related  to the purposes set out above and, in any event, so as to guarantee the  protection and confidentiality of your personal data.    
**   
3\. Providing personal data and consequences of a possible refusal  **  
Providing your personal details is voluntary. However, your refusal and/or providing incorrect or incomplete information might result in the impossibility for you to register to the store.ferrari.com website and benefit of the related contents and services, as well as in the impossibility for the Companies to manage and/or execute your purchase orders or any other  services for which it is necessary to process your personal data.  
**  
4\. Communication of information**     
Within the Companies your personal data may be disclosed to the companies' officers and bodies, to the personnel and particularly the employees who develop the products, deal with customer care services or marketing activities, manage the website and technical mantainance and, in any event, the person in charge and the data processors.  
Your personal data may be communicated to any qualified persons who provide services or functions to Ferrari for the purposes mentioned above, including the persons and companies who manage and/or take part in the management and/or handling of our websites and the electronic and/or telematic instruments we use.  
For the same purposes as above, the Companies may also disclose your personal data to the following categories of persons and/or companies: parent companies, controlled and/or participating companies; qualified subjects who supply the Company with assistance and services, in particular in relation to the management of the website and technical mantainance or the consignment of products.  
For the same purposes as above your personal data may be disclosed to:   
parent companies, controlled and/or participating companies; sales network in Italy and abroad; qualified subjects such as, for example, banks, firms and insurance companies, suppliers and sub-contractors who supply the Company with assistance and services used for the management of your purchase order and/or after sales services,  for carrying out of statistic and market surveys, for the organisation and holding of events, including of a promotional nature, for sending sales communications, experts who assist the Company in various ways by referring in particular to the legal, tax, contingency accounting and organisational aspects; any other person to whom the information should be given in accordance with an express legal provision. Your personal information may be transferred abroad, in accordance with the current regulations including in Countries not belonging to the European Union where the Company works in its own interest.    
**  
5\. Data dissemination**  
Your personal information will not be disseminated.   
**  
6\. Rights of the person concerned**  
Concerning the above data processing, you may exercise the following rights:   
\- obtain the confirmation of the existence or non-existence of personal information concerning  yourself, even if it is not yet recorded, and its communication in an understandable form.    

  You have the right to obtain the indication:   
\- of the origin of the personal information;   
\- of the purpose and terms and conditions of the processing;   
\- of the logic applied in the processing carried out with the use of electronic instruments;   
\- of identification details of the Controller and the people in charge;  
\- of subjects or categories of subjects to whom personal information can be given or who may become aware of such information. 

  You also have the right to obtain:   
\- the updating, the alteration or, when of interest, the integration of data;   
\- the cancellation, transformation in an anonymous form or the blocking of information processed by breach of the law, including any information whose preservation is not necessary compared with the purposes for which the information has been collected or processed at a later date;    
\- the certificate attesting that the operations provided for above have been made known, including with regard to their content, to the persons to whom the information was given or distributed, except in the event that such execution is impossible or includes the use of means obviously out of proportion with the protected right. 

  You have the right to oppose, in all or part:   
\- for legitimate reasons, the processing of personal information concerning him/her, even if it concerns the purpose of its collection;    
\- the processing of personal information concerning him/her so as to send advertising materials or for direct sales or the realisation of market research or sales communication.

  **7\. Data Controllers**      
The Data Controllers are  
Ferrari S.p.A., the registered office of which is in Via Emilia Est, n° 1163, Modena (Italy), premises in via Abetone Inferiore 4, 41053 Maranello-MO (Italy), and  
triboo digitale s.r.l., the registered office of which is in V.le Sarca 336, 20126 Milano (Italy)  
Any request in relation to personal information processed by Ferrari S.p.A. and/or triboo digitale s.r.l. may therefore be addressed to the following electronic address customercare@ferraristore.com.  
**   
8\. Consent   **  
The present information note will be submitted to you either when you register to the website or when you submit a purchase order without registration. On that occasions you will be asked to consent to the processing of Your personal data by Ferrari and triboo digitale s.r.l..  
By consenting to Ferrari and triboo digitale s.r.l. the processing of your personal information   under terms and conditions set above,  including the communication to the persons mentioned and/or the transfer abroad, you will: allow the managing of Your registration and access to the 'store.ferrari.com' website; take advantage of services, contents and activities especially reserved to registered users; allow the managing and executing of your purchase orders; take advantage of the assistance services and/or after-sales warranties; allow the reply to your requests and the sending of technical/organisational communications.

   You may also separately consent to the processing of your personal data by Ferrari and triboo digitale s.r.l. in accordance with the terms and conditions and for the purposes described  above concerning, namely,  allowing you to take part to events including those of a promotional nature; carrying out statistical and market surveys and research; receiving information and/or promotional communication, including commercial information, advertising material and/or offers of goods and services, in particular our newsletter, through the Post, Internet, telephone, e-mail, MMS, SMS, exclusively by Ferrari and/or parent companies and/or allied companies or by any person or legal entity collaborating in the business activities of Ferrari, triboo digitale s.r.l. included.
